<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Campaign 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>lib\media\favicon.png</url><title>Campaign 2</title><link/></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 13:50:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="lib\rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 13:50:06 GMT</pubDate><copyright><![CDATA[TF997]]></copyright><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator>TF997</dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[Combat Cheat Sheet]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>Initiative determines the order of turns during combat. When combat starts, every participant rolls Initiative. <br><br>On your turn you can do <br>
<br>1 Action 
<br>1 Bonus Action 
<br>Move
<br>Small amount of communication
<br>Minor interaction. 
<br>A turn is 6 seconds of time "in game" so communication and minor interaction should take this in to context.<br><br>
<br>Attack (With a weapon or Magic)
<br>Dash (Double your movement)
<br>Disengage (No attacks of opportunity against you this turn)
<br>Dodge (Adv to Dex saving throws and attacks against you are at disadvantage until next turn)
<br>Help (Help another creature’s ability check or attack roll, or administer first aid)
<br>Hide (Stealth)
<br>Influence (Make a Wis or Cha check to persuade a creature)
<br>Ready (Hold an action until a specific trigger occurs)
<br>Search (Wis check)
<br>Study (Int check)
<br>Utilize (Use a non magical object. eg pick up a chair)
<br><br>these are class specific but can include casting spells with a time of 1 BA or being able to hide if you're a rogue.]]></description><link>the-library\handouts\combat-cheat-sheet.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Library/Handouts/Combat Cheat Sheet.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TF997]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 13:49:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Locations]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>General Goods &amp; Services:<br>
<br>The Crooked Crow General Store:  Owned by Elara Thistlewood. Sells basic supplies, tools, rope, fishing<br>
gear, and some mundane magical items (like healing potions).
<br>Raven's Rest Inn &amp; Tavern:  Run by the gruff but kind-hearted Bjorn Ironforge. Offers lodging, hearty meals,<br>
ale, and a lively atmosphere with occasional bard performances.
<br>The Wandering Merchant: Owned by the enigmatic Faylen. Travels between towns selling exotic goods, rare herbs, spices, and occasionally, unique magical trinkets.
<br>Specialty Shops:<br>
<br>Spellbound Apothecary:  Owned by the wise herbalist, Anya Silverleaf. Specializes in healing potions, remedies, poisons, and unusual ingredients for brewing magic.
<br>The Blacksmith's Forge: Run by the stoic Gareth Hammerhand. Crafts weapons, armor, tools, and performs repairs.
<br>Silversong's Emporium: Owned by the elegant Lyra Silversong. Sells fine fabrics, clothing, jewellery, perfumes, and other luxury goods.
<br>Unique Shops:<br>
<br>The Bookworm's Burrow:  Owned by the eccentric scholar, Professor Hemlock. A haven for books, scrolls, maps, and arcane texts. He might also know a thing or two about ancient secrets.
<br>Whispers of the Wind Curios: Owned by the mysterious Elara Duskwood.  Sells unusual artifacts, enchanted objects, strange trinkets, and perhaps even whispers of forbidden knowledge.
]]></description><link>the-library\lore\ravenford\locations.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Library/Lore/Ravenford/Locations.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TF997]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 13:38:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Backstory Questionnaire]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>1. Origin:<br>
<br>Where is your character originally from?

<br>Are they a native of Ravenford, or did they migrate here? If so, from where and why?


<br>2. Family and Early Life:<br>
<br>What is known about your character’s family?

<br>Are they still in contact with their family? What is/was their relationship like?
<br>Did any family members play a significant role in shaping who they are today?


<br>3. Significant Events:<br>
<br>What are one or two defining moments in your character’s past that set them on the path to becoming an adventurer?

<br>How did these events influence their beliefs, skills, or goals?


<br>4. Profession and Skills:<br>
<br>What training or education has your character received?

<br>Do they have a particular set of skills or a profession they practiced before becoming an adventurer?
<br>How did they acquire these skills?


<br>5. Connection to Ravenford:<br>
<br>What ties does your character have to Ravenford?

<br>Do they have any significant relationships, debts, or affiliations within the town?
<br>How do they feel about the mystical and historical significance of Ravenford?


<br>6. Personal Motivation:<br>
<br>Why is your character drawn to adventuring?

<br>Are they seeking wealth, knowledge, power, redemption, or perhaps something more personal?
<br>How does this motivation influence their actions and choices?


<br>7. Attitudes and Beliefs:<br>
<br>What are your character’s key beliefs and values?

<br>How do they view the balance between order and chaos, especially in a place influenced by both?
<br>Are there any particular laws or traditions in Ravenford or Talonmere that they strongly support or oppose?


<br>8. Friends and Foes:<br>
<br>Does your character have any allies or enemies in Ravenford or elsewhere in Talonmere?

<br>How did these relationships come to be?
<br>What impact have these relationships had on their life?


<br>9. Personal Secrets:<br>
<br>What is something secretive or unknown about your character that could affect their journey?

<br>Does your character have any hidden agendas or unresolved personal quests?


<br>10. Future Aspirations:<br>
<br>What does your character hope to achieve through their adventures?

<br>Where do they see themselves after their adventures in Talonmere are over?


]]></description><link>the-library\handouts\backstory-questionnaire.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Library/Handouts/Backstory Questionnaire.md</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[TF997]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 10:00:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Orbris, The God Of Chaos]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Orbris.webp" src="lib\media\orbris.webp"><br>
In the primordial void, before light carved its dominion over darkness, there stirred Orbris, the Embodiment of Chaos. Neither malevolent nor benign, Orbris dances on the edge of creation and oblivion, weaving the fabric of existence into ever-shifting patterns. To invoke Orbris is to invite the whirlwind, to court the storm that rends the veil between potential and reality. Followers seek not Orbris's favor, for such a concept is foreign to the deity; instead, they aspire to become conduits for the primal chaos, to shape and be shaped by the eternal flux.<br>In the age of Talonmere, Orbris is worshipped, feared, and courted by those who understand the true nature of power—not as a throne to be claimed but as a storm to be directed. <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The Library/The Ancients/The Eldritch Conclave" data-href="The Library/The Ancients/The Eldritch Conclave" href="the-library\the-ancients\the-eldritch-conclave.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Eldritch Conclave</a>, in their quest for demi-godhood, believes that by harnessing the essence of Orbris, they can transcend their mortal coils and achieve a state of divine chaos.<br>Orbris's places of worship are as varied as the aspects of chaos, hidden in the chaotic sprawls of cities, in alleys that twist upon themselves, leading pilgrims on a journey without end. Each shrine is an anomaly, defying the laws of nature and magic—water flows uphill, flames freeze, and shadows cast light.<br>A common sigil is the Ouroboros, a serpent eating its own tail, representing the endless cycle of creation and destruction. Other symbols include fractals, representing the infinite complexity of chaos, and the spiral, a motif that signifies the unpredictability and constant motion inherent to Orbris's nature.]]></description><link>the-library\gods\orbris,-the-god-of-chaos.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Library/Gods/Orbris, The God Of Chaos.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 09:34:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\orbris.webp" length="0" type="image/webp"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\orbris.webp"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ravenford]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><br>
<br>Origin of Ravenford: The town was said to be founded at the crossing of the Black Stone Bridge, where the ancient ravens first guided the settlers to a safe haven across the wild river.
<br>The Ravens: Local legend holds that the ravens in Ravenford are not mere birds but the souls of ancient warriors who protect the town. Their presence is a sign of the town's continued safety and prosperity.
<br>Black Stone Bridge Lore: It is believed that the bridge has mystical properties, changing color under the moonlight to warn of impending danger or significant events.
<br><br>
<br>The Festival of Wings: An annual festival in Ravenford celebrating the ravens. It includes wearing feathered masks, storytelling, and a night of remembrance for ancestors and past heroes, reinforcing the town's spiritual connection with the ravens.
<br>The Dance of Shadows on the Bridge: A local tradition where on the longest night of the year, people gather on the Black Stone Bridge to watch the interplay of light and shadow, believed to bring good luck and foresight into the future.
]]></description><link>the-library\lore\ravenford\ravenford.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Library/Lore/Ravenford/Ravenford.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 09:32:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Talonmere]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br>
<br>Formation of Talonmere: Tales of cosmic battles between forces of order and chaos leading to the formation of the land, with Ravenford often highlighted as a place where the balance between these forces is most visible.
<br>The Ancient Races: Knowledge that long ago, the Inarii and the Eldritch Conclave shaped much of the world’s history with their advanced technology and dark magic, respectively. The stories might be vague but underscore a sense of mystery and caution about the ruins and artifacts they left behind.
<br>The Role of the Watchers: While details may be scarce, there is an understanding that the Watchers guard significant ancient sites, built by the Inarii to protect their powerful artifacts.
<br>Kingdom Unification: Awareness of how the various towns and regions, including Ravenford, came together under a single banner to form the current kingdom, driven by a need for mutual protection and prosperity.
]]></description><link>the-library\lore\talonmere.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Library/Lore/Talonmere.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 09:33:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Eldritch Conclave]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Eldritch.webp" src="lib\media\eldritch.webp">In the ancient annals of Talonmere's history, a small but sinister group of warlocks emerged, their souls bound by a dark pact with the deity <a data-href="Orbris, The God Of Chaos" href="the-library\gods\orbris,-the-god-of-chaos.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">Orbris, The God Of Chaos</a>, the god of chaos and disorder. This clandestine assembly, known as the Eldritch Conclave, delved into forbidden realms of the arcane, seeking to harness the chaotic energies that coursed through the cosmos.<br>Driven by a thirst for power that bordered on madness, the members of the Conclave embarked on a perilous quest to unlock the secrets of the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The Library/The Ancients/The Inarii" data-href="The Library/The Ancients/The Inarii" href="the-library\the-ancients\the-inarii.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Inarii</a>, ancient engineers whose technological marvels lay scattered across Talonmere. These artifacts, imbued with both mystical properties and advanced engineering, held the key to untold power, power that the Conclave believed could unchain Orbis from its prison in the Nine Hells.<br>Yet, despite their dark ambitions, the Conclave's efforts were thwarted by the complexity and enigmatic nature of <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The Library/The Ancients/The Inarii" data-href="The Library/The Ancients/The Inarii" href="the-library\the-ancients\the-inarii.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Inarii</a>'s creations. Frustration turned to desperation as their dreams of godhood seemed to slip through their grasp. In their obsession, they delved deeper into the forbidden arts, sacrificing their humanity in pursuit of their dark desires.<br>Though the Conclave's presence may have faded from Talonmere, the echoes of their dark legacy reverberate through the ages. Their insidious influence continues to shape the course of history, their machinations lurking in the shadows, waiting for the day when they shall return to claim their rightful place as masters of chaos and disorder.]]></description><link>the-library\the-ancients\the-eldritch-conclave.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Library/The Ancients/The Eldritch Conclave.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 09:36:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\eldritch.webp" length="0" type="image/webp"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\eldritch.webp"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Inarii]]></title><description><![CDATA[ 
 <br><img alt="Inarii.webp" src="lib\media\inarii.webp"><br>The Inarii were an enigmatic group of ancient beings who possessed unparalleled knowledge of engineering and arcane sciences. They were renowned for crafting powerful artifacts imbued with both technological marvels and mystical properties. These artifacts, scattered throughout the continent of Talonmere, held immense power and were coveted by many.<br>Before departing from the planet, the Inarii constructed sophisticated machines capable of traversing the astral plane, allowing them to explore distant galaxies in search of new knowledge and realms. However, in their absence, they left behind guardians known as the Watchers. These enigmatic beings were tasked with protecting the ancient artifacts and preventing them from falling into the hands of malevolent forces, particularly the <a data-tooltip-position="top" aria-label="The Library/The Ancients/The Eldritch Conclave" data-href="The Library/The Ancients/The Eldritch Conclave" href="the-library\the-ancients\the-eldritch-conclave.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener">The Eldritch Conclave</a>, a sinister group seeking to harness forbidden powers for their own dark purposes.<br>Though the existence of the Watchers is referenced in ancient texts and lore, they have remained elusive, veiled in mystery and myth. Many adventurers and scholars have sought to uncover their secrets, but the Watchers have never been found, their presence only hinted at through cryptic tales and whispers from ages past. As the artifacts of the Inarii continue to surface, the need for the Watchers’ protection becomes increasingly vital, ensuring that the balance of power remains undisturbed and the secrets of the ancients remain safeguarded.]]></description><link>the-library\the-ancients\the-inarii.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">The Library/The Ancients/The Inarii.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2024 09:36:16 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="lib\media\inarii.webp" length="0" type="image/webp"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src="lib\media\inarii.webp"&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>